ugetfix.com 2019-05-10

# Privacy policy

Our privacy policy discloses the following conditions related to your personal information and privacy.

## Gathering information

UGetFix gathers the following information from its users:

  * Registration information when user participates in forums or subscribes to the newsletter;
  * Information required to post comments or leave us questions.

Email addresses provided in the appropriate fields are NEVER disclosed to third parties, except when required by law. We can not protect your data if you enter it in fields available for the public view, such as forum posts or comment posts.

Like almost any website in the world, we use analytic packages for improving our site and troubleshooting various problems. They include:

  * Google Analytics. You can download google analytics opt-out tool here http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout if you have problems with that. Google analytics uses cookies.
  * Hey.lt (shows aggregate information of unique users and total views only).
  * Server logs.

## Cookies

You understand that UGetFix might use session cookies to allow you the access to specific features of the site that require being logged in (e.g., forum).

Besides, UGetFix may show advertisements and 3-rd party content which might use cookies for providing the best value to our visitors. This includes, but is not limited to:

  * AddThis content sharing platform;
  * Google Adsense/DFP and Kontera advertising networks;
  * Affiliate networks to attribute software downloads (Revenuewire.com, OneNetworkDirect.com, cj.com, linkshare.com, Cleverbridge.com element5, and some other networks).
  * Analytics packages, covered above.

This is done to identify the source of visitors or provide customized browsing experience. We are not responsible for the information they collect. If you want to avoid this, you can disable cookies or allow them one by one. However, some of our discounts offered on the page might be disabled if the user disables cookies.

## Data protection and its use

There are cases when we can not provide safety for your personally identifiable information. This statement is related to optional information, and you are the only one who is here to decide whether you should make it public or not. We do not take responsibility for the safety and privacy of such information. If you leave it in public on our website or share it with other members of this community, we are not responsible for the following consequences. We also are not responsible for illegally-disclosed information from third parties.

Note that we can only disclose your information to third parties only if we consider this procedure as necessary. It may be disclosed to governmental authorities if we find it necessary.

The security of your information is extremely important to us. We ensure you that we will take care of technical, administrative, and physical security measures to protect your information from unauthorized access and improper use.

However, note that, despite our best efforts, no security measures are perfect these days. There is a small possibility that we might sell or merge it with another business. In such cases, the information we gathered (aka Google Analytics data, comments, server logs and other information) might be among the transferred assets.

## Linked sites and advertisements

In an attempt to provide you with valuable service, we may include third party links on our site. UGetFix.com expects all linked sites to respect the privacy of its users.

Be aware that third parties may have their privacy policy and may use different data collection methods. UGetFix is not responsible for actions or policies of any other site. Some of the advertisers might collect information to determine if you saw the advertisement before, or use it in other ways for improving your experience.

## Site Use

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

## Contacting us

If you have any questions, related to Privacy Policy, you can contact us by using this [Contact Us form](https://ugetfix.com/contact-us/). To know more about this project, check [About us](https://ugetfix.com/about-us/), [Agreement of Use](https://ugetfix.com/agreement-of-use/), [Disclaimer](https://ugetfix.com/disclaimer/), and [Disclosure](https://ugetfix.com/disclosure/).
